<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Barrington Brook: Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Barrington Brook: Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AMI refresh automation project</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/ami-refresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/ami-refresh/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 12 Dec 22
When a new Amazon Machine Image (AMI) is generated we need to update all of our instances with this new AMI. This can be quite a time consuming job so it was decided in a team day towards the end of the year that we would find a way to automate it. The first ticket for this work was to design and implement a process for refreshing auto-scaling groups in AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Presentation for Portfolio Team</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/presentation/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 27 Jul 22
We were tasked with presenting the work of the Hack team as well as an introduction to DevOps practices and technologies more generally to a non-technical audience.
The Audience was a portfolio team whose interests included our work but who didn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily have any technical background.
How did we get the ticket? The portfolio team had been conducting a series of meetings where a representative from another team and explained in layman’s terms how they worked and what it was that they were concerned with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gold Standard Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/gold-standard-pipeline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/gold-standard-pipeline/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 21 Mar 23
It had been decided in our organisation that we would migrate our repositories from a self-hosted gitlab instance to a SaaS solution on gitlab.com. There are a number of benefits to this but mainly you are saving time spent mangaging it. Having a self hosted instance can have some benefits mostly to do with customisation. K24.
Software solutions Enterprise: A solution where software is purchased from some company and then installed on your organisations servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hashicorp support request</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/hashicorp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/hashicorp/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 21 Mar 23
Our team provides support to a number of developer teams and every week we select one person to be the main port of call to deal with support requests. On one of my fortnights on support duty, I received a support request that required me to make a support request to Hashicorp, an external organisation that supports a number of our infrastructure tools. The request was do to a developer experiencing unexpected behaviour while using hashicorp nomad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mongo Access Request</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/mongo-db/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/mongo-db/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 21 June 23
Article 25 of GDPR (Data protection by design and by default) requires that we &amp;ldquo;&amp;hellip;implement appropriate technical and organisational measures for ensuring that, by default, only personal data which are necessary for each specific purpose&amp;rdquo;
For example, our databases are divided by project and environment (which are called different organisations in mongo) and within these &amp;ldquo;organisations&amp;rdquo; different users have different abilities.
Below you can see evidence of a ticket where I am granting temporary access to another organisation for a user who has sufficient security clearance and a clear use case for accessing this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peer Review</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/peer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/peer-review/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 28 Mar 23
In our team, peer review is an important part of our development process so we can ensure that we maintain a high level of quality for the code we commit since we are continually improving our systems and make a large number of changes in a relatively short space of time. It is of paramount importance that when reviewing anothers work that we are mindful of the principles of a blameless culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>README automation demonstration</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/readme-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/readme-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In our repositories the READMEs were often not helpful and contained outdated information. Furthermore, no uniform style was applied. My task was to design and implement an automated process that would remedy this issue.
My solution I decided that I would create a Gitlab CI pipeline to collate information from a number of sources and then create a README and push to the same repository from the Gitlab runner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/training/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 21 March 23
Introduction I believe that continuous learning is very important in this role. Alongside training required by the Civil Service (e.g. health and safety, regualatory training). I also have taken several training courses as well as availed myself of online training courses that I have access to as part of my job.
DWP training completed As can be seen below I have completed a course in data protection (Think Secure: Security and Data Protection at DWP) mandated by DWP.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
