<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>K22 on Barrington Brook: Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/tags/k22/</link>
    <description>Recent content in K22 on Barrington Brook: Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://barringtonbrook.github.io/tags/k22/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My Team I am a DevOps engineer apprenctice in Hack IT and Whip IT team within Universal Credit, DWP digital. We are the DevOps team that build and support infrastructure for products and projects on HCL2 and UC platforms. Within our team, there is a delivery manager, team Lead, several seniors, one junior and four apprentices. We work closely with the feature teams in Leeds and Manchester. These teams include developers, QAs (testing engineers), delivery managers and architects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/training/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 21 March 23
Introduction I believe that continuous learning is very important in this role. Alongside training required by the Civil Service (e.g. health and safety, regualatory training). I also have taken several training courses as well as availed myself of online training courses that I have access to as part of my job.
DWP training completed As can be seen below I have completed a course in data protection (Think Secure: Security and Data Protection at DWP) mandated by DWP.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
