<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Barrington Brook: Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Barrington Brook: Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://barringtonbrook.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My Team I am a DevOps engineer apprenctice in Hack IT and Whip IT team within Universal Credit, DWP digital. We are the DevOps team that build and support infrastructure for products and projects on Burbank and UC platforms. We work closely with the Feature Teams in Leeds and Manchester.
We are currently using the scrum framework to organise and manage our work. That means we have decide on sprint tickets in week/two week blocks, have daily scrum meetings as well as retrospectives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Presentation for Portfolio Team</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/presentation/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 27 Jul 22
We were tasked with presenting the work of the Hack team as well as an introduction to DevOps practices and technologies more generally to a non-technical audience.
The Audience was a portfolio team whose interest included are work but who didn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily have any technical background.
How did we get the ticket? The portfolio team had been conducting a series of meetings where a representative from another team and explained in layman’s terms how they worked and what it was that they were concerned with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge, Skills and Behaviours</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/ksbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/ksbs/</guid>
      <description>Knowledge KSB Description Tickets K3 How to use data ethically and the implications for wider society, with respect to the use of data, automation and artificial intelligence within the context of relevant data protection policy and legislation. - K6 A range of problem solving techniques appropriate to the task at hand, such as affinity mapping, impact maps, plan-do-check-act/Deming. - K9 Different organisational cultures, the development frameworks utilised and how they can both complement each other and introduce constraints on delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
