<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Barrington Brook: Portfolio</title>
    <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Barrington Brook: Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://barringtonbrook.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My Team I am a DevOps engineer apprenctice in Hack IT and Whip IT team within Universal Credit, DWP digital. We are the DevOps team that build and support infrastructure for products and projects on Burbank and UC platforms. We work closely with the Feature Teams in Leeds and Manchester (K18).
We are currently using the scrum framework to organise and manage our work. That means we have decide on sprint tickets in week/two week blocks, have daily scrum meetings as well as retrospectives (S8).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMI refresh automation project</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/ami-refresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/ami-refresh/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 12 Dec 22
When a new Amazon Machine Image (AMI) is generated we need to update all of our instances with this new AMI. This can be quite a time consuming job so it was decided in a team day towards the end of the year that we would find a way to automate it. The first ticket for this work was to design and implement a process for refreshing auto-scaling groups in AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS RDS support request</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/aws-support-request/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/aws-support-request/</guid>
      <description>S2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Presentation for Portfolio Team</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/presentation/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 27 Jul 22
We were tasked with presenting the work of the Hack team as well as an introduction to DevOps practices and technologies more generally to a non-technical audience.
The Audience was a portfolio team whose interests included our work but who didn&amp;rsquo;t necessarily have any technical background.
How did we get the ticket? The portfolio team had been conducting a series of meetings where a representative from another team and explained in layman’s terms how they worked and what it was that they were concerned with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving Access</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/giving-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/giving-access/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 21 Mar 23
I gave someone access to our systems K3
(Name Removed)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knowledge, Skills and Behaviours</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/ksbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/ksbs/</guid>
      <description>Knowledge KSB Description Tickets K3 How to use data ethically and the implications for wider society, with respect to the use of data, automation and artificial intelligence within the context of relevant data protection policy and legislation. - K6 A range of problem solving techniques appropriate to the task at hand, such as affinity mapping, impact maps, plan-do-check-act/Deming. - K9 Different organisational cultures, the development frameworks utilised and how they can both complement each other and introduce constraints on delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peer Review</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/peer-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/peer-review/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 28 Mar 23
This is an example of a comment: K23 B4</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Problem Solving Techniques</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/problem-solving/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/problem-solving/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 28 Mar 23
K20</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>README automation demonstration</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/readme-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/readme-presentation/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In our repositories the READMEs were often not helpful and contained outdated information. Furthermore, no uniform style was applied. My task was to design and implement an automated process that would remedy this issue.
My solution I decided that I would create a Gitlab CI pipeline to collate information from a number of sources and then create a README and push to the same repository from the Gitlab runner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self directed learning</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/self-directed-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/self-directed-learning/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Date: 21 March 23
The course below is one I completed. S16 B2
I also use Pluralsight to maintain and awareness and prepare for certification. K25</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traefik Pipeline Consolidation</title>
      <link>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/traefik-pipeline-consolidation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://barringtonbrook.github.io/posts/traefik-pipeline-consolidation/</guid>
      <description>Introduction It had been decided in our organisation that we would migrate our repositories from a self-hosted gitlab instance to a SaaS solution on Gitlab.com. There are a number of benefits to this but mainly you are saving time spent mangaging it. Having a self hosted instance can have some benefits mostly to do with customisation which K24.
K18.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
